fullodisha.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy - Odia Services

We respect your privacy and we are committed to protect the same. We do not publish, sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes. The privacy practices of this statement apply exclusively to our services available under the domain and sub-domains of www.fullodisha.com and apply generally to our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries or joint venture websites. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our website. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Terms of Use Agreement. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance in registration for new registering users, and is otherwise effective on carrying out any transaction with us for all users. In the course of registering for and availing various services we provide from time to time through our website (Website, telephone search, SMS and WAP or any other medium in which Fullorissa may provide services (collectively referred to as “Media”) you may be required to disclose your name, residence address, email address, telephone number and similar Personal Information (“Personal Information”). Your Personal Information is used for two general purposes: to process your order, and to provide you with the best possible services. Unless otherwise stated explicitly, this Policy applies to Personal Information as disclosed on any of the Media. In furtherance of the confidentiality with which we treat your Personal Information we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use data collection devices such as “cookies” on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. “Cookies” are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a “cookie”. We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are “session cookies,” meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Site and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session. Additionally, you may encounter “cookies” or other similar devices on certain pages of the Site that are placed by third parties. For example, if you view a web page created by a user, there may be a “cookie” placed within that web page. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties. You acknowledge that you are disclosing Personal Information voluntarily. Prior to the completion of any registration process on our website or prior to availing of any services offered on our website if you wish not to disclose any Personal Information you may refrain from doing so; however if you don’t provide information that is requested it is possible that the registration process would be incomplete and/or you would not be able to avail of the our services. Fullorissa, through its website, is extremely proud of it’s commitment to protect your privacy. We value your trust in us. We will work hard to earn your confidence so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to friends and family. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Site. Fullorissa promises that we will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Your trust and confidence are our highest priority. Personal Information may be shared only under one or more of the following circumstances: (a) If we have your consent or deemed consent to do so; (b) If we are compelled by law (including court orders) to do so. Fullorissa gives you the ability to edit your account information and preferences at any time. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. Further, you have the right to refuse any marketing email from us or any other trader in the future.
